ws1.com 2013-07-20

# Privacy Policy

**What information do we collect?**

When placing an order or registering for our site, you may be asked to provide your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, and billing information.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used to process your transactions and to send you periodic emails. Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.  The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order.  We offer the use of a secure server. All sensitive information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes.  Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your web browser, if you allow, that enables web sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and remember certain information.  We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor's information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://www.worldship1.com/en/agreement//

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

© 2009-2013 © WS1.com / Digital Commerce (USA) LLC | All rights reserved.
